<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Settings</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>

    <!-- home -->
    <string name="audio_profiles">Audio profile</string>
    <string name="wifi">WLAN</string>
    <string name="data_usage">Data usage</string>
    <string name="bluetooth">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="sensor">Sensor</string>
    <string name="ptt">PTT talk</string>
    <string name="display">Display</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="security_and_password">Security and password</string>
    <string name="date_time">Data &amp; time</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="about_bike">About bike</string>
    <string name="unbind_bike">Unbind bike</string>
    <string name="input_box_title">Lesports</string>

    <!-- data -->
    <string name="data_on">On</string>
    <string name="data_off">Off</string>
    <string name="data_of_the_rest">Residual flow of this month</string>
    <string name="data_of_use">The use of this month</string>

    <!-- security -->
    <string name="lockscreen_password">Lock screen password</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_password_tip">Need to enter a password or fingerprint</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_password_tip_no_fingerprint">Need to enter a password</string>
    <string name="password_manager">Password setting</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_manager">Fingerprint manager</string>
    <string name="password_input">Enter password</string>
    <string name="password_input_check_new">Verify new password</string>
    <string name="password_not_match">Password is not consistent, please re-enter</string>
    <string name="password_wrong">Password is wrong, please re-enter</string>
    <string name="password_set_success">Password set successfully</string>
    <string name="password_close">Disable password</string>
    <string name="password_verify">Password verify</string>

    <!-- fingerprint -->
    <string name="fp_manager">Fingerprint manager</string>
    <string name="fp_add_fp">Add fingerprint</string>
    <string name="fp_del_fp">Are you sure to delete fingerprint ?</string>
    <string name="fp_enroll_tip">Please pick up and drop your finger again and again until the completion of the 100% entry</string>
    <string name="fp_enroll_tip2">The fingerprint has been added \n you can use the fingerprint to unlock the super bike</string>
    <string name="fp_fp1">Fingerprint 1</string>
    <string name="fp_fp2">Fingerprint 2</string>
    <string name="fp_fp3">Fingerprint 3</string>
    <string name="fp_fp4">Fingerprint 4</string>
    <string name="fp_fp5">Fingerprint 5</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_0">0</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_1">1</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_2">2</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_3">3</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_4">4</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_5">5</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_6">6</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_7">7</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_8">8</string>
    <string name="password_keyboard_9">9</string>

    <!-- wifi -->
    <string name="wifi_please_open">Turn on WLAN to see available network</string>
    <string name="wifi_current_select">Current connection:</string>
    <string name="wifi_candidate">Select network</string>
    <string name="wifi_on">On</string>
    <string name="wifi_oning">Wlan is turning on ......</string>
    <string name="wifi_off">Off</string>
    <string name="wifi_offing">Wlan is turning off ......</string>
    <string name="wifi_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="wifi_show_password">Display</string>
    <string name="wifi_input_password">Enter password</string>

    <!-- ppt -->
    <string name="ptt_please_open">Turn on PTT to choose intercom channel</string>
    <string name="ptt_channel_select">Current channel:</string>
    <string name="ptt_channel">Channel</string>
    <string name="ptt_on">On</string>
    <string name="ptt_off">Off</string>

    <!-- audio -->
    <string name="audio">Audio profile</string>
    <string name="ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>

    <!-- display -->
    <string name="display_title">Display</string>
    <string name="brightness">Brightness</string>
    <string name="brightness_autio_adjust">Automatic brightness</string>
    <string name="save_mode">Power saving mode</string>
    <string name="save_mode_detail">Automatically lock screen after 1 minute without operation in non riding condition</string>

    <!-- date_time -->
    <string name="date_time_title">Date &amp; time</string>
    <string name="auto_set_date_time">Automatic date &amp; time</string>
    <string name="auto_set_date_time_detail">Use network-provided time</string>
    <string name="auto_set_timezone">Automatic time zone</string>
    <string name="auto_set_timezone_detail">Use network-provided time zone</string>
    <string name="manual_set_date">Set date</string>
    <string name="manual_set_time">Set time</string>
    <string name="manual_set_timezone">Set time zone</string>
    <string name="cancel_date">Cancel</string>
    <string name="finish_date">OK</string>
    <string name="timezone_set">Time zone setting</string>
    <string name="no_date_dispaly">Please set date</string>
    <string name="no_time_display">Please set time</string>
    <string name="no_timezone_display">Please set time zone</string>
    <string name="year">/</string>
    <string name="month">/</string>
    <string name="day">" "</string>
    <string name="Sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="Monday">Monday</string>
    <string name="Tuesday">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="Wednesday">Wednesday</string>
    <string name="Thursday">Thursday</string>
    <string name="Friday">Friday</string>
    <string name="Saturday">Saturday</string>

    <!-- usb_connect -->
    <string name="charge_only">Charge only</string>
    <string name="media_charge">Media and charge</string>

    <!-- ringtone -->
    <string name="ring_default">Opening (default)</string>
    <string name="ring_wave">Waves</string>
    <string name="ring_beacon">Beacon</string>
    <string name="ring_blink">Twinkle</string>
    <string name="ring_knock">Tapping</string>

    <!-- about -->
    <string name="about_help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_q01">Q&#038;A</string>
    <string name="help_q02">如何联系客服？</string>
    <string name="help_a1">拨打电话1010-9000。</string>
    <string name="help_q2">如何进行系统升级？</string>
    <string name="help_a2">请保持联网状态，若有新的版本，系统会自动提醒您进行升级。
        您也可以手动在设置-关于自行车-系统版本中进行新版本检索和升级，
        在升级过程中请保证您的自行车有足够的电量</string>
    <string name="help_q3">忘记自行车密码怎么办？</string>
    <string name="help_a3">请牢记自己设定的自行车密码，如果真的忘记，请联系我们的客服寻求帮助</string>
    <string name="help_q4">我应该在骑行状态时使用智能功能吗？</string>
    <string name="help_a4">为了您的安全，请切勿在骑行中操作自行车的智能功能，请停下车来使用这些功能</string>
    <string name="help_q5">为什么心率检测有时候有显示有时候没显示？</string>
    <string name="help_a5">心率检测需要手握住30-60秒才能显示，且需静止时才有效。
        心率传感器是通过容易受到静电、肌肉电、震动、电磁干扰等影响，可能会时有失灵情况。</string>
    <string name="help_q6">为什么自行车耗电很快？</string>
    <string name="help_a6">智能自行车有很多传感器，相应的也有较大的电量消耗，
        我们也会在后续版本中优化电量消耗，请随时更新系统</string>
    <string name="help_q7">为什么磨电花鼓有时候无法充电？</string>
    <string name="help_a7">Shimano前轮发电花鼓,电机额定功率为6V 3W，在骑行时可正常充电，磨电花鼓工作时的实际发电功率跟骑行速度相关，骑行速度在20-30km/h，方可达到额定充电功率。
        大部分骑行时间磨电花鼓充电功率低，因此其仅可作为辅助充电方法，充电主要靠外接充电线充电。</string>
    <string name="help_q8">如何添加收听本地音乐？</string>
    <string name="help_a8">通过数据线连接，把mp3格式音乐拷贝到自行车sd卡的music文件夹中，就可以收听对应离线音乐。</string>
    <string name="help_q9">指纹识别如何使用，为何有时指纹录入失败?</string>
    <string name="help_a9">需要首先设置安全密码，才能使用指纹识别快速解锁功能。指纹需要多次按压才能完成录入指纹，
        使用时，请保持手指干燥，按照提示轻轻按压指纹区域。</string>
    <string name="help_q10">为什么没有车撑子和挡泥板？</string>
    <string name="help_a10">为减轻重量，标配无支架和挡泥板，高端自行车一般都是如此。如有需要可自行配置</string>
    <string name="help_q11">自行车PTT对讲的功能，可否通过调频实现与其它手台或对讲机对讲？</string>
    <string name="help_a11">可以。将其他手台将频率调至自行车所设置的频点时即可对讲</string>
    <string name="help_q12">超级自行车是否可以更换其他SIM卡？</string>
    <string name="help_a12">超级自行车已经为您配备定制的SIM卡，提供定向流量，卡机绑定，请勿更换卡，
        后续的版本中，我们还将为您提供流量充值等功能，敬请期待</string>
    <string name="help_q13">历史骑行数据会丢失或覆盖吗？</string>
    <string name="help_a13">我们的骑行数据存储于乐视云服务器中，只要不删除就不会丢失</string>
    <string name="help_q14">没电的情况下还能骑行吗？</string>
    <string name="help_a14">若电子锁没有锁定，可以正常骑行。但如果您的电子锁处于锁定状态，需要先充电，才能解除电子锁的锁定并骑行</string>

    <!-- 语言 -->
    <string name="language_chinese">中文</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>

    <!-- 使用条款 -->
    <string name="tos_home_title">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="tos_item_1">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="tos_item_2">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="tos_content_1">Welcome to LeEco.  We and our group of affiliated companies provide websites, features on websites, 
        and other products and services when you use or purchase from our websites, or use our products or software.  
        These Terms of Service govern your purchase, access and use of products and services offered by or on behalf of Le Technology, 
        Inc. and its Affiliates (“LeEco”, “we” or “us”), including those offered or provided on mobile phones, televisions, TV Boxes, accessories, 
        websites, and software, including mobile applications (“LeEco Services”). For the purposes of these Terms of Service,
         “Affiliate” means the group of entities which are controlling, controlled by or under common control with Le Technology, 
         Inc., and “control” means possessing, directly or indirectly, the power to direct or cause the direction of the management, 
         policies or operations of an entity, whether through ownership of voting securities, by contract or otherwise.\n\n
         By purchasing or using any LeEco Services you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms of Service, including the arbitration 
         agreement and class action waiver described below. Please read them carefully.\n\n
         We offer a range of products and services, and additional terms and fees may apply to particular LeEco Services. 
         Those additional terms will be available with the relevant LeEco Services and become part of your agreement with us if you use those 
         LeEco Services. In case of a conflict between these Terms of Service and those additional terms, the additional terms will control for 
         that conflict.\n\n
         These Terms of Service are intended for users and purchasers of LeEco Services located in North America,
          including the United States of America, including its territories and possessions (collectively, the “United States”), Canada and Mexico.  
          If you have purchased, accessed or used a LeEco Service outside North America, please consult the applicable LeEco terms and 
          conditions for your territory.  To the extent that there are conflicts between the applicable LeEco terms and conditions for your 
          territory and these LeEco Terms of Service for North America, the applicable LeEco terms and conditions for your territory will control. \n\n 
         1.MINIMUM AGE\n\n
         LeEco Services may provide access to content, products or services that are not appropriate for children under the age of 14.
          Persons under the age of 14 may only access or use LeEco Services under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian.\n\n
          2.PRIVACY\n\n
          Personally identifying information is subject to our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated and made a part of these Terms of Service. 
           Please review our Privacy Policy at www.leeco.com/privacy to understand how we collect and use your information when you use LeEco Services.\n\n
          3.NOTICES FROM LEECO\n\n
          If LeEco needs to contact you about your LeEco Services or account, by signing up for or using any LeEco Services, 
          you consent to receive the notices electronically in the manner consistent with the contact information you provide, including email, 
          text messages, or other communications between your desktop or mobile device and us.  You agree that any notices, agreements, 
          disclosures or other communications that we send to you electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements, 
          including that those communications be in writing.\n\n
          4.USING LEECO SERVICES\n\n
          a.Access.  Subject to your compliance with these Terms of Service and your payment of any applicable fees, LeEco grants you a limited, 
          non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicensable right to access and make personal and non-commercial use of the LeEco Services.  
          Additionally, the software license terms found below apply to any software (including any updates or upgrades to the software and any 
          related documentation) that we make available to you from time to time for your use in connection with LeEco Services. No portion of the 
          LeEco Services may be reproduced in any form or by any means. You agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, 
          or create derivative works based on the LeEco Services, in any manner, and you will not exploit the LeEco Services in any unauthorized way
           whatsoever, including but not limited to, using the LeEco Services to transmit any computer viruses, worms, Trojan horses or other malware,
            or by trespass or burdening network capacity. You further agree not to use the LeEco Services in any manner to harass, abuse, 
            stalk, threaten, defame or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party, and that LeEco is not in any way responsible for 
            any such use by you.\n\n
            b.Accounts and Security.  Use of the LeEco Services may require an account ID and may be subject to fees and different or additional 
            terms depending on the service.  You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account ID and password for each 
            LeEco Service.  You agree to notify us immediately at Privacy-US@le.com of any unauthorized use or theft of your account or any 
            other breach of security.  You are responsible the activity that happens on or through your account.  \n\n
            c.Cloud Services. If LeEco offers cloud services and you register for cloud services, certain cloud features, including, but not limited to, 
            cloud photo library, photo stream, cloud photo sharing, back up and phone locator functionality may be accessed directly from the
             LeEco Services.  Your use of cloud services and these features is subject at all times to the terms and conditions of the cloud services as 
             made available to you and updated from time to time.\n\n
             d.Sync. If you choose to use any synchronization (“sync”) features included as part of the LeEco Services to synchronize your bookmarks, 
             notes, collections, and blog or podcast subscription data across your LeEco Services and devices, you acknowledge that data related to
              those sync features will be sent to LeEco and stored in conjunction with your LeEco account ID in order to sync among the devices that
               are authorized to access synced content through your account ID. \n\n
               e.Content. By using any of the LeEco Services, you may encounter content, including content, data, information, applications or 
               materials from third parties (“Third Party Materials”), including materials provided by other users, bloggers and third-party licensors, 
               syndicators, aggregators and/or reporting services, or links to web sites or applications.  All statements and/or opinions expressed 
               in these materials, and all articles and responses to questions and other content, other than the content provided by the LeEco, 
               are solely the opinions and the responsibility of the person or entity providing those materials. These materials do not necessarily 
               reflect the opinion of the LeEco, and may contain subject matter or language that is not appropriate for all ages, so viewer discretion 
               is advised. While we do not review all content, we may review and remove content that we believe violates our policies or applicable law.  
               We do not assume responsibility or liability to you or any other person for third-party services, Third Party Materials or third party web 
               sites or applications, or for any other materials, products, or services of third parties. To the extent you choose to use or access any 
               LeEco Services and Third Party Materials, you are responsible for your compliance with any applicable laws, including territory restrictions.\n\n
               f.Limitations on the Services. LeEco Services and Third Party Materials that may be accessed, linked to or displayed in the LeEco Services 
               are not available in all languages, countries or regions. Neither LeEco nor any of its content providers guarantees the availability, accuracy, 
               completeness, reliability, or timeliness of stock information, location data or any other data displayed by any LeEco Services and such 
               information should not be relied upon as accurate.  LeEco and its licensors reserve the right to change, suspend, remove, or disable 
               access to any LeEco Services at any time with or without notice. LeEco may impose limits on the use of or access to certain LeEco Services,
                for any reason and without notice or liability.\n\n
                5.SOFTWARE LICENSE TERMS\n\n
                The following software license terms apply to any software (including any updates or upgrades to the software and any related 
                documentation) that we make available to you from time to time for your use in connection with LeEco Services.\n\n
                a.General.  The software (including embedded software and third party software), documentation, interfaces, content, fonts and any 
                data that came with your device or that is provided to you as part of LeEco Services, as applicable (the “Original LeEco Software”), 
                as may be updated or replaced by feature enhancements, software updates or system restore software provided by 
                LeEco (the “LeEco Software Updates”), whether in read-only memory, on any other media or in any other form (the Original LeEco 
                Software and LeEco Software Updates are collectively referred to as the “LeEco Software”) are licensed, not sold, to you by or on 
                behalf of LeEco for use only under the terms of these Terms of Service. LeEco and its licensors retain ownership of the LeEco Software 
                and reserve all rights not expressly granted to you in this License. You agree that the terms of this License will apply to any LeEco 
                Software, unless it is accompanied by a separate license, in which case you agree that the terms of that separate license will govern 
                your use of that software or application.\n\n
                LeEco, in its discretion, may make available future LeEco Software Updates for your device. 
                The LeEco Software Updates, if any, may not necessarily include all existing software features 
                or new features that LeEco releases for newer or other models. The terms of this License will govern any LeEco Software Updates 
                provided by LeEco that replace and/or supplement the Original LeEco Software, unless such LeEco Software Update is accompanied by a 
                separate license, in which case the terms of the separate license will govern.\n\n
                b.Permitted License Uses and Restrictions. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, you are granted a limited non-exclusive 
                license to use the LeEco Software on a single device. Unless provided in a separate agreement between you and LeEco, this License does not allow the LeEco 
                Software to exist on more than one device at a time, and you may not distribute or make the LeEco Software available over a network where 
                it could be used by multiple devices at the same time. This License does not grant you any rights to use LeEco proprietary interfaces or other 
                technology or intellectual property in the design, development, manufacture, licensing or distribution of third party devices or accessories, 
                or third party software applications, including for use with any LeEco Service. \n\n
                You may not, and you agree not to or permit or assist others to, copy (except as expressly permitted by this License), decompile, 
                reverse engineer, disassemble, attempt to derive the source code of, decrypt, modify, or create derivative works of the LeEco Software 
                or any services provided by the LeEco Software or any part thereof (except as and only to the extent these restrictions are prohibited by 
                applicable law).\n\n
                Automatic application updates may be available for the LeEco Software, and if you choose to allow automatic application updates, 
                your LeEco Software will periodically check with LeEco for updates to the apps on your device and, if one is available, the update will 
                automatically download and install onto your device. \n\n
                c.Transfer.  You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute, or sublicense the LeEco Software. You may, however, make a one-time, 
                permanent transfer of all of your license rights to the LeEco Software to another party in connection with the transfer of ownership 
                of your associated LeEco device, provided that: (a) the transfer must include your LeEco device and all of the LeEco Software, including
                 all its component parts, original media and this License; (b) you do not retain any copies of the LeEco Software, full or partial, including 
                 copies stored on a computer or other storage device; and (c) the party receiving the LeEco Software reads and agrees to accept the 
                 terms and conditions of this License.\n\n
                 d.Export Control.  You must comply with all export and re-export restrictions and regulations of the Department of Commerce and other United States agencies and authorities that may apply to the LeEco Software. You also agree that you will not use the LeEco Software for any purposes prohibited by United States law.\n\n
                 e.Government End Users.  The LeEco Software and related documentation are “Commercial Items,” as that term is defined at 48 C.F.R. §2.101, consisting of “Commercial Computer Software” and “Commercial Computer Software Documentation,” as such terms are used in 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202, as applicable. 
                 Consistent with 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202-1 through 227.7202-4, as applicable, the Commercial Computer Software and Commercial Computer Software Documentation are being licensed to U.S. Government end users (a) only as Commercial Items and (b) with only those rights as are granted to all other end 
                 users pursuant to these Terms of Service. Unpublished rights are reserved under the copyright laws of the United States.\n\n
                 6.MOBILE DEVICES AND MOBILE DEVICE APP PERMISSIONS\n\n
                 Some LeEco Services may be available on mobile devices.  Do not use these services in such a way that causes distraction and prevents you from observing and obeying traffic or other safety laws and regulations. When you use apps provided by us, you may grant certain permissions to us for your device. Most mobile devices 
                 provide you with information about these permissions and how they can be changed or disabled.\n\n
                 7.LEECO PRODUCT AND SERVICES INFORMATION\n\n
                 The information presented on or through LeEco websites is made available solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to an LeEco website, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.\n\n
                 8.PROPRIETARY RIGHTS\n\n
                 a.Ownership. All information, content, materials, products (including software), text, graphics, logos, images, audio or visual clips, complications of content and other services included in or otherwise made available to you through the LeEco Services (collectively, the “LeEco Content”) are proprietary works owned by LeEco or its content providers and are protected by U.S. and international intellectual property laws.  All right, title and interest in and to the LeEco Content, including, but not limited to, all copyright, moral rights, patent, patent registration, service mark, service name, trade name, trade secret, trademark, or other proprietary right arising or enforceable under any United States federal or state law, rule or regulation, non-United States law, rule or regulation or international treaty, is the exclusive property of LeEco or its content providers.  All rights not expressly granted to you in these Terms of Service are reserved and retained by LeEco or its content providers.  Your use of LeEco Content, including, news, entertainment and other content offered by LeEco, is limited solely to your personal, noncommercial use, does not transfer any ownership interest to you in the LeEco Content, and specifically excludes, without limitation, any commercial or promotional use rights in the LeEco Content.  Except as otherwise expressly provided in an application, you may not republish, retransmit or reproduce any images accessed through any application.\n\n
                 b.Trademark Use.  The name LeEco, LeTV, LeMall.com and all related names, logos, product and service names, designs and slogans, and website elements, designs and scripts are trademarks or trade dress of LeEco and its affiliated companies. LeEco’s trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not ours, in a manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, that dilutes its uniqueness, or that disparages or discredits us. All other names, logos, product and service names, designs and slogans accessible through LeEco are the property of their respective owners.\n\n
                 c.User Content. To the extent that you upload any content through the use of the LeEco Services, you represent and warrant that you own all rights in, or have the legal right to upload, such content and that such content does not violate these Terms of Service or any other terms applicable to the LeEco Services and that the uploaded content is not obscene, illegal, threatening, infringing any copyright, trademark, right of publicity or other intellectual property right, defamatory, violative of privacy rights or otherwise objectionable.  LeEco is free to use any comments, information, ideas, concepts, reviews, or techniques or any other material contained in any communication you may send to us (“Feedback”), including responses to questionnaires or through postings to the LeEco Services, including the LeEco websites, applications and user interfaces, worldwide and in perpetuity without further compensation, acknowledgement or payment to you for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and creating, modifying or improving the LeEco Services. In addition, you agree not to enforce any “moral rights” in and to the Feedback, to the extent permitted by applicable law. \n\n
                 9.COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT AND DMCA\n\n
                 If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any content, information, or communication on the LeEco Services, including any content posted by a user, infringes upon your copyrights, you may submit a written notice of infringement pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. § 512 (the “DMCA”). \n\n
                 All notices of infringement should be sent to the Designated Agent of LeEco identified below and should include the following information: \n\n
                 (a) an electronic or physical signature of the copyright owner or of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest,\n
                 (b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed, \n
                 (c) a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Site, \n
                 (d) your address, telephone number, and e-mail address, \n
                 (e) a written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law, and\n
                 (f) a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.\n
                 For the fastest processing of your request, written notice should be sent to our designated agent via our online copyright complaint form at www.leeco.com/dmca. \n\n
                 Alternatively, notices of infringement should be directed to the following Designated Agent of LeEco:\n
                 LeEco\n
                 Attn. Legal Director - IP\n
                 3553 N. 1st Street\n
                 San Jose, CA 95134\n\n
                 If you submit a notice of infringement that knowingly materially misrepresents that any LeEco Content, information, or communication on the LeEco Services is infringing upon a copyright, you may be held liable for damages and attorneys’ fees. If you believe that your content, information, or communication has been removed from the LeEco Services due to an erroneous claim of infringement, you may have remedies available to you under the DMCA.\n\n
                 It is the policy of the LeEco to terminate the user accounts of repeat infringers.\n\n
                  10.THIRD PARTY TERMS. \n\n
                  Portions of the LeEco Services may utilize or include third party software and other copyrighted material. Your use of third party material is governed by the respective terms of those third parties. \n\n
                  11.DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n\n
                  TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE LEECO SERVICES AND ALL INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) AND OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE LEECO SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE”, WITH ALL FAULTS AND WITHOUT WARRANTY, GUARANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND, AND LEECO AND LEECO’S LICENSORS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE LEECO SERVICES OR INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) AND OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE LEECO SERVICES, EITHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES AND/OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, ACCURACY, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. LEECO AND LEECO’S LICENSORS DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE OPERATION OF THE LEECO SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT ANY LEECO SERVICE WILL CONTINUE TO BE MADE AVAILABLE, THAT DEFECTS IN THE LEECO SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE LEECO SERVICES WILL BE COMPATIBLE OR WORK WITH ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES. INSTALLATION OF SOFTWARE CONTAINED IN THE LEECO SERVICES MAY AFFECT THE AVAILABILITY AND USABILITY OF THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES, AS WELL AS LEECO SERVICES.\n\n
                  LEECO DOES NOT ASSUME ANY LIABILITY FOR PURCHASES, PAYMENTS, TRANSACTIONS, OR OTHER ACTIVITY USING PAYMENT FEATURES OF THE LEECO SERVICES, AND YOU AGREE TO LOOK SOLELY TO AGREEMENTS YOU MAY HAVE WITH YOUR ISSUING BANK, PAYMENT NETWORK, OR MERCHANT TO RESOLVE ANY QUESTIONS OR DISPUTES RELATING TO YOUR SUPPORTED CARDS, VIRTUAL SUPPORTED CARDS AND ASSOCIATED COMMERCE ACTIVITY.\n\n
                  TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL LEECO, ITS AFFILIATES OR LICENSORS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, AGENTS OR PRINCIPALS BE LIABLE FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, CORRUPTION OR LOSS OF DATA, FAILURE TO TRANSMIT OR RECEIVE ANY DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR ANY OTHER COMMERCIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE LEECO SERVICES OR ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE OR APPLICATIONS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE LEECO SERVICES, HOWEVER CAUSED, REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY (CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE), EVEN IF LEECO HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, IN NO EVENT WILL LEECO’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES (OTHER THAN AS MAY BE REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW IN CASES INVOLVING PERSONAL INJURY) EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF TWO HUNDRED AND FIFTY DOLLARS (U.S. $250.00). THESE LIMITATIONS ARE INTENDED TO APPLY EVEN IF THE FOREGOING REMEDY IS FOUND TO HAVE FAILED OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.\n\n
                  IF ANY PROVISION OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE IS HELD TO BE INVALID, ILLEGAL, OR UNENFORCEABLE, THE VALIDITY, LEGALITY AND ENFORCEABILITY OF THE REMAINING PROVISIONS WILL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.\n\n
                  CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN KINDS OF DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.\n\n
                  12.GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION\n\n      
                  You agree that Federal Arbitration Act, applicable United States federal law, and the laws of the State of California, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Service and any dispute or claim arising between you and LeEco.  The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods will not apply to these Terms and Conditions.\n\n
                  13.ADDITIONAL TERMS\n\n
                  We reserve the right to make changes to the terms of our applicable privacy and other policies, these Terms of Service, and other applicable terms of use at any time. If any applicable terms shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, such term shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining terms.\n\n
                  14.ARBITRATION AGREEMENT AND CLASS ACTION WAIVER\n\n
                  If you are a user of the LeEco Services in the United States (including its possessions and territories), you agree that exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute, claim, or demand related in any way to the Contest will be decided by binding arbitration. All disputes between you and LeEco, of whatsoever kind or nature arising out of these Terms of Service, shall be submitted to JAMS, Inc. (“JAMS”) for binding arbitration under its rules then-in-effect in the San Jose, California, USA area, before one arbitrator to be mutually agreed upon by both parties.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, you have the right to an in-person hearing in your hometown area. This agreement to arbitrate is intended to be broadly interpreted and includes, but is not limited to any dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or relating in any way to these Terms of Service or your use of the LeEco Services.  The U.S. Federal Arbitration Act will govern the interpretation and enforcement of this provision, and you and LeEco each waive the right to a trial by jury or to participate in a class action.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, either party may bring an individual action in small claims court. This arbitration provision does not preclude the user from bringing issues to the attention of federal, state, or local agencies. Such agencies can, if the law allows, seek relief against LeEco on your behalf. \n\n
                  Except as otherwise provided herein, or unless LeEco and you agree otherwise, any arbitration hearings will take place by video or telephone conference.  For the avoidance of doubt, the arbitration shall allow for the discovery or exchange of non-privileged information relevant to the dispute.  Regardless of the manner in which the arbitration is conducted, any Arbitrator’s Award will consist of a written statement stating the disposition of each claim, and the arbitrator shall issue a reasoned written statement of the essential findings and conclusions on which the award is based.  The arbitrator is not authorized to award punitive or other damages not measured by the prevailing party’s actual damages, and may not, in any event, make any ruling, finding or award that does not conform to the terms and conditions of these Terms of Service. \n\n
                  Except as expressly set forth herein, the payment of all filing, administration and arbitrator fees will be governed by the JAMS’ rules, and if you initiate the arbitration, you shall only be responsible for fees up to US $250.00.  All other costs will be borne by LeEco, including any remaining JAMS Case Management Fee and all professional fees for the arbitrator’s services.  If LeEco initiates the arbitration, LeEco shall pay all fees associated with the arbitration. \n\n
                  YOU AND LEECO AGREE THAT EACH MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN YOUR OR LEECO’S INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. Further, unless both you and LeEco agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person’s claims with your claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of a representative or class proceeding. If this specific provision is found to be unenforceable, then the entirety of this arbitration provision shall be null and void. The arbitrator may award declaratory or injunctive relief only in favor of the individual party seeking relief and only to the extent necessary to provide relief warranted by that party’s individual claim.\n\n
                  Notwithstanding the foregoing, the parties acknowledge and agree that any violation of LeEco’s proprietary rights in the LeEco Services or LeEco Software by you would cause irreparable harm and significant injury, the degree of which may be difficult to ascertain. Accordingly, each party agrees that in the event of your violation of LeEco’s proprietary rights in the LeEco Services or LeEco Software as provided in these Terms of Service, LeEco shall not be required to submit such claims to arbitration, and LeEco shall have the right to seek an immediate injunction from any court of competent jurisdiction enjoining any such violation of LeEco’s proprietary rights in the LeEco Services or LeEco Software. \n\n
</string>
    <string name="tos_content_2"> Le Technology, Inc. and its Affiliates, which are referred to collectively as “LeEco”, “we” or “us” in this Privacy Policy, know that you care how information about you is used.  For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Affiliate” means the group of entities which are controlling, controlled by or under common control with Le Technology, Inc., and “control” means possessing, directly or indirectly, the power to direct or cause the direction of the management, policies or operations of an entity, whether through ownership of voting securities, by contract or otherwise. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information is collected and how that information is used when you visit our websites or use our products and services, including mobile phones, televisions, TV Boxes, accessories, websites, and software, including mobile applications (“LeEco Services”).  Some LeEco Services shall provide and be subject to a different privacy policy than the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy, and in such event, the terms of the applicable LeEco Service privacy shall supersede this Privacy Policy.\n\n
        By visiting our websites or using the LeEco Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, including the arbitration agreement and class action waiver described below. \n\n
        This Privacy Policy applies to you if (1) you are located in the United States and use any LeEco Service or (2) if you are located anywhere in the world and visit our websites including leeco.com or any of our other websites or LeEco Services based in or hosted from the United States. If you are located outside of the United States and have purchased, visited, or used any LeEco Service, you should consult the applicable LeEco Services Privacy Policy for your territory for other terms that may apply to you with respect to LeEco Services you receive outside the United States.  Before using and submitting information through the LeEco Services, please read this Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the LeEco Services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies identified in this Privacy Policy and consent to having your personal and non-personal information transferred to and/or processed as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the LeEco Services.\n\n
       1. Information We Collect\n\n
       We collect information to personalize your experience of the LeEco Services and to provide and improve our service sand products.\n\n
       The following are the types of information we collect:\n
       Information that you provide to LeEco.  We collect information you enter in your use of LeEco Services or give us, our affiliates or business partners.  For example, when you create an account sign up for a subscription or purchase a product from LeEco, we will ask you for personal information such as your name, birthdate, address, phone number, email address or credit card to store with your account. \n
       Information we obtain from your use of LeEco Services.  We collect information about how you use the LeEco Services, like when you visit our websites, use our software, or interact with our devices. This information includes: \n
       Device and user activity.  We may collect information including:\n
       device information such as device identifiers, hardware capabilities, and network information including phone number\n
       details of how your used our services, such as content queries\n
       Internet protocol (IP) addresses\n
       devices events such as crash events, log files, hardware settings, and source and referral URLs. \n
       Location-based data.  When you use the LeEco Services, we may receive information about your location, for example, using information about your computer, product or mobile device, including GPS, WiFi, IP address or other unique identifiers. This location data may be used by LeEco and our partners to provide and improve location-based products and services, such as advertising and other personalized content. \n
       Cookies. “Cookies” are small files sent to your computer when you visit a website. They can store information like user preferences and other information. When you use a LeEco Service, we may use a cookie, web beacons, or other similar technology to record information about how you use the LeEco Service, such as geographic and language preferences, the effectiveness of ads, or the content query that directed you to a particular page. We may use cookies in conjunction with advertising to provide you with personalized content. Most browsers allow you to delete cookies and not accept new ones. However, disabling them may prevent you from using certain LeEco features or functionality. \n\
       Video data. When you activated your use of video within the LeEco Services, you consented to our collection of information regarding the videos accessed.  If you wish to withdraw your consent, please disable use of the video-related LeEco services through your device’s system settings. However, some of the LeEco Services may not function correctly if the video-related LeEco services are disabled.\n\n
       2.How We Use Information We Collect\n\n
       We use the information we collect to to allow us to efficiently process your transactions, to provide, maintain, protect, improve, LeEco Services, and to develop new services and products. We may use personal and non-personal information across LeEco Services you use. We may use this information to personalize the LeEco Services, and to help us deliver personalized services and advertising of interest to you.\n\n
       For example, we may use your personal information to send you communications, to personalize your LeEco Services, to make sharing of information and content easier for you (such as content uploaded through social media), to verify your age or identity, for security, error reporting, service restriction, loss prevention, and anti-fraud purposes, and to help us to create, to develop, to operate, to deliver and to improve our products, services, content and advertising. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, analysis of your online activities over time, and research to improve the LeEco Services and customer communications.\n\n
       We also collect information in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual, including de-identified or aggregated information collected regarding customer activities on the LeEco Services. We may collect, use, transfer, store and disclose this non-personal information for any purpose. We treat information collected by cookies as non-personal information as long as it can’t be used to identify a particular individual.  If we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information under this Privacy Policy. \n\n
       3.Disclosures to Third Parties\n\n
       At times, LeEco may make certain personal information available to affiliates, partners, or venders that work with LeEco to provide products and services, process payments, analyze data, provide customer service, and help LeEco market to customers. These companies may be located anywhere in the world, including outside of your country of residence.\n\n
       We also may work with partners to help us deliver LeEco ads to you on third-party websites, applications or devices. We may share information we collect from you with these partners. To deliver these ads, our partners may collect information about you, your devices, and your use of LeEco Services. This information may include visits to websites and use of applications provided by LeEco and others, your IP address, your Internet service provider, and the browser that you use to visit our websites.\n\n
       It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from international, national, federal, state, public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for LeEco to disclose your personal information or other information. We may also disclose your personal information if we determine that for purposes of national security, public safety, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.\n\n
       We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or to protect us, our products and services, our partners, operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, stock sale, merger, sale or divestiture of all or any part of our business, operations or assets, change of control, or a financing or bankruptcy or liquidation, we may transfer or disclose information, including personal information, to a third party in connection with those events.\n\n
       4.Children’s Privacy\n\n
       We do not knowingly intend to collect personal information from children under 14 years of age. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may send an email message to Privacy-US@le.com with “Request for Child Information Removal” on the subject line and the name and age of the child in the body of the message.  We will then make reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from the database that stores information for the applicable LeEco Services.\n\n
       5.Protection of Personal Information\n\n
       We care about the security of your information and take steps to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to your personal information. If you become aware of any technical vulnerability affecting LeEco Services or have any concerns, please email Privacy-US@le.com. \n\n
       6.Retention of Personal Information\n\n
       We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required by law or for business-related reasons. We may retain non-personal information indefinitely, including following termination or suspension of your LeEco accounts, memberships or subscriptions. We will take commercially reasonable steps to erase or destroy any Personal information stored on any LeEco devices you return to us in accordance with industry standards, but we cannot guarantee that all such personal information will be completely removed from returned devices. Accordingly, you should take care to ensure all personal information is permanently removed from your LeEco devices prior to returning devices to us. \n\n
       7.Integrity and Access to Personal Information\n\n
       You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your LeEco account.  You may also request access to your other personal information held by LeEco, such as to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if LeEco is not required to retain it by law or permitted to retain it for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by contacting us at Privacy-US@le.com. \n\n
       8.Third—Party Sites and Services\n\n
       LeEco Services may contain advertisements for and links to third-party websites, applications, products, and services, including through “plug-ins,” widgets, buttons, and other third party features or integrations made available on and connected with LeEco Services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties − for example, content and applications. Information collected by third parties, location data and contact details, is governed by the privacy practices of those third parties. LeEco is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those third-party websites, applications, products or services and this Privacy Policy does not govern the use or disclosure of any information you choose to disclose to third parties. \n\n
       9.International Transfer and Access; Users From Outside the United States\n\n
       All information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. Information that we collect may be stored on your device or stored on our servers and transferred to, stored and processed in the United States or any other country where LeEco or its service providers maintain facilities, including jurisdictions that may not have data privacy laws that provide protections equivalent to those provided in your home country. By using the LeEco Services, you consent to your information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.\n\n
       10.Privacy Questions\n\n
       If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or LeEco’s collection, use, disclosure, transfer or storage of your information, or if you would like to notify us about a possible breach of security or local privacy laws, please contact us at Privacy-US@le.com.  \n\n
       LeEco may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. You should look at these terms regularly. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen (14) days after they are posted. Your continued use of applicable websites and LeEco Services after the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of those updates. \n\n
       11.Arbitration Agreement and Class Action Waiver  \n\n
       If you are a visitor of our websites or user of the LeEco Services and subject to this Privacy Policy, you agree that all disputes and claims between you and LeEco will be settled by binding arbitration instead of in courts of general jurisdiction as provided in our Terms of Service located at www.leeco.com/generalTerms.\n\n
       12.Applicable Law and Venue\n\n
       By using any LeEco Service, you agree that the Federal Arbitration Act, applicable federal law, and the laws of the state of California, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern this Privacy Policy and any dispute of any kind that might arise between you and LeEco. In the event that this Section 12 is severed in any legal action, then the parties agree that any legal relief sought will be brought in the federal or state courts serving Santa Clara County, California.\n\n
       13.Survival\n\n
       If any provision or provisions of this Privacy Policy are held to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions will remain in full force and effect.\n\n
</string>

    <!-- 关于 -->
    <string name="about_sys_version">System version</string>
    <string name="about_model">Model number</string>
    <string name="about_mac">Wi-Fi Mac address</string>
    <string name="about_ip">IP address</string>
    <string name="about_imei">IMEI</string>
    <string name="about_version_2">Build number</string>

    <!-- 电量 -->
    <string name="battery_less_than_15">Less than 15% of electricity</string>
    <string name="battery_less_than_5">Less than 5% of electricity</string>
    <string name="battery_to_power_off">Power depletion, is about to shut down</string>
    <string name="battery_unlock">Unlock</string>

</resources>
